PONGSAKAN OBROMKIN

DEVELOPER



- 096-884-5847
- pongsakan.o@hotmail.com
- 2 467 m.5 Samut prakan, Thailand
- https://pongsakan-profile.netlify.app
- https://github.com/pskfdev

PROFILE

Hello, my name is Pongsakan Obromkin, I currently work as a technician at Future lifestyle. I'm interested in the position of front-end developer. I've been learning to for 1 year for react, html, css, js, and other. And i want to increase my experience and ready to learn in this field.

HARD SKILLS

- HTML
- JS (ES6)
- REACT JS
- AXIOS
- CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind, Mui)
- OTHER(Git, Figma, Photoshop)

SOFT SKILLS

- CREATIVITY
- COLLABORATION
- PROBLEM SOLVING
- POSITIVE ATTITUDE
- EMOTIONAL INTELLIGENCE

EXPERIENCE

TECHNICIAN (SMART HOME)

Future Lifestyle co.,ltd

2019 - Present

- Site survey.
- Manage claim.
- · Coding (Lua).
- Install and configure devices(FIBARO).
- Support for using the device and application.
- Performed miscellaneous duties, which are work-related as assigned.

WEBSITE BARBER SHOP (FRONT-END)

It is a project made as a result of practicing coding a website using the React framework.

- HTML
- CSS (Style component)
- JS (ES6)
- Fetch API
- React is

WEBSITE FOOD ZERO (FULLSTACK)

It is a project made as a result of practicing coding a MERN Stack website.

- HTML
- CSS (Bootstrap, Sass)
- JS (ES6)

Express is

• React is

- Axios
- MongoDB

2015 - 2018

Node is

EDUCATION

MATHEMATICS-SCIENCE

Samutprakan School

2012 - 2015

COMPUTER SCIENCE

Rajamangala University of Technology Thanyaburi